this trial that Olga has won, which was the one she had
este juicio que ha ganado Olga que era
left to win, this
ya el que le quedaba por ganar esto
belongs to the trial they held in
pertenece está el juicio que hicieron en
November and they took photos of her, very
noviembre y le hicieron las fotos muy
worried at the door of the courthouse. I
preocupada en la puerta del juzgado me
remember, I remember that, well now the
acuerdo me acuerdo de eso pues ahora el
result of the trial is not being
resultado del juicio no lo pone en
published, this trial that you are seeing, no,
lectura este juicio que estáis viendo no
that Rosito called for that, she files the
que rosito llamó para eso pone la
lawsuit to make headlines, that is, she calls
demanda para sacar titulares o sea llama
the press, yes, she
a la prensa sí
calls the press so that her little
Llamar a prensa para que sus amiguitos
reading friends can get the exclusive, the
de lectura saquen la exclusiva la
photograph, no, and inside it was like Olga did
fotografía no y por dentro era como Olga
n't look at her face, Olga was afraid,
no le ha mirado la cara Olga tenía miedo
Olga, I don't know what, and now they won't give the sentence, that we
Olga no sé qué y ahora la sentencia no
were commenting on it, that
la dan que lo estuvimos comentando que
we were like, well, they have
nos quedamos como bueno se les ha